{
"1" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( tables ) ENGINE=InnoDB AUTO_INCREMENT=797 DEFAULT CHARSET=utf8mb4 COLLATE=utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci;", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( tables ) ENGINE=InnoDB AUTO_INCREMENT=797 DEFAULT CHARSET=utf8mb4 COLLATE=utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci;"},
"2" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'ID' bigint(20) unsigned NOT NULL AUTO_INCREMENT );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'ID' bigint(20) unsigned NOT NULL AUTO_INCREMENT );"},
"3" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_author' bigint(20) unsigned NOT NULL DEFAULT '0' );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_author' bigint(20) unsigned NOT NULL DEFAULT '0' );"},
"4" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_date' datetime NOT NULL DEFAULT '0000-00-00 00:00:00' );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_date' datetime NOT NULL DEFAULT '0000-00-00 00:00:00' );"},
"5" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_date_gmt' datetime NOT NULL DEFAULT '0000-00-00 00:00:00' );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_date_gmt' datetime NOT NULL DEFAULT '0000-00-00 00:00:00' );"},
"6" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_content' longtext CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_content' longtext CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL );"},
"7" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_title' text CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_title' text CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL );"},
"8" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_excerpt' text CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_excerpt' text CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL );"},
"9" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_status' varchar(20) CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL DEFAULT 'publish' );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_status' varchar(20) CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL DEFAULT 'publish' );"},
"10" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'comment_status' varchar(20) CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL DEFAULT 'open' );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'comment_status' varchar(20) CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL DEFAULT 'open' );"},
"11" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'ping_status' varchar(20) CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL DEFAULT 'open' );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'ping_status' varchar(20) CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL DEFAULT 'open' );"},
"12" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_password' varchar(255) CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL DEFAULT '' );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_password' varchar(255) CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL DEFAULT '' );"},
"13" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_name' varchar(200) CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL DEFAULT '' );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_name' varchar(200) CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL DEFAULT '' );"},
"14" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'to_ping' text CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'to_ping' text CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL );"},
"15" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'pinged' text CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'pinged' text CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL );"},
"16" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_modified' datetime NOT NULL DEFAULT '0000-00-00 00:00:00' );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_modified' datetime NOT NULL DEFAULT '0000-00-00 00:00:00' );"},
"17" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_modified_gmt' datetime NOT NULL DEFAULT '0000-00-00 00:00:00' );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_modified_gmt' datetime NOT NULL DEFAULT '0000-00-00 00:00:00' );"},
"18" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_content_filtered' longtext CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_content_filtered' longtext CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL );"},
"19" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_parent' bigint(20) unsigned NOT NULL DEFAULT '0' );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_parent' bigint(20) unsigned NOT NULL DEFAULT '0' );"},
"20" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'guid' varchar(255) CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL DEFAULT '' );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'guid' varchar(255) CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL DEFAULT '' );"},
"21" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'menu_order' int(11) NOT NULL DEFAULT '0' );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'menu_order' int(11) NOT NULL DEFAULT '0' );"},
"22" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_type' varchar(20) CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL DEFAULT 'post' );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_type' varchar(20) CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL DEFAULT 'post' );"},
"23" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_mime_type' varchar(100) CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL DEFAULT '' );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'post_mime_type' varchar(100) CHARACTER SET utf8mb4 COLLATE utf8mb4_unicode_520_ci NOT NULL DEFAULT '' );"},
"24" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'comment_count' bigint(20) NOT NULL DEFAULT '0' );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( 'comment_count' bigint(20) NOT NULL DEFAULT '0' );"},
"25" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( PRIMARY KEY ('ID') );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( PRIMARY KEY ('ID') );"},
"26" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( KEY 'post_name' ('post_name'(191)) );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( KEY 'post_name' ('post_name'(191)) );"},
"27" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( KEY 'type_status_date' ('post_type','post_status','post_date','ID') );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( KEY 'type_status_date' ('post_type','post_status','post_date','ID') );"},
"28" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( KEY 'post_parent' ('post_parent') );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( KEY 'post_parent' ('post_parent') );"},
"29" : {"question": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( KEY 'post_author' ('post_author') );", "rightAnswer": "CREATE TABLE 'wp_posts' ( KEY 'post_author' ('post_author') );"}

}